[Music]
[Música]
Okay, let's see what Rebor did, eh, what a
Bueno vamos a ver lo de rebor eh vaya
collection of
recogida de
Cabletec, from
cabletec de
Cabletech, I mean, a contrast from
cabletech o sea un un contraste del
white to black but like that, bang, dry,
blanco al negro pero así en pum en Seco
there, without warning, you know, like when the
ahí sin sin avisar sabes como cuando se
water heater runs out, many
te va el termo de la bombona hace muchos
years ago I don't have a gas cylinder, not at home,
años ya que no tengo bombona no en casa
but when I had it, the gas
pero cuando la tenía no se te acababa la
cylinder never ran out. Holy crap, holy crap,
bombona me cago en la [__] me cago en 10
no, and now all of a sudden, Oh, F made a
no y ahora de repente Oh F se ha
mistake, Luare and Luare are here today. Aliado
equivocado luare y luare hoy está Aliado
is not here. F the millionaire picked up the
no está aquí F el millonario recogió
cable. Yeah, let's see, he picked it up. Well, I
cable Sí es que a ver ha recogido Bueno
have it on Twitter, let's see, he picked up the
lo tengo en Twitter a ver ha recogido
cable, eh, but it's like very, eh. Let's see,
cable eh pero es como muy no eh A ver
one thing is for you to say, come on, Auron has
una cosa es que digáis venga auron ha
come. Turn off the fire, let's be
venido Apaga el fuego vamos a estar
cordial. We're not going to make a fuss or whatever,
cordialmente No la vamos a liar o lo que
but from there, I don't
sea no pero ya de ahí a a chuparnos los
think so either. eh, I mean, there's no
penes tampoco creo eh o sea no hay un
extreme, there's a middle ground, not like,
extremo hay un hay un punto medio no en
Look, okay, you go this way, I'll go that
plan de Mira vale tú por aquí yo por
way, we'll leave each other alone. No, but that's it. It's not like
allá nos dejamos en paz No pero ya eso
anything has happened here.  we
de No es que aquí no ha pasado nada nos
love each other this year has been an avalanche
queremos este año ha sido una avalancha
eh very strange since 7 or 8 months is
eh muy rara desde hace 7 o8 meses es
when the mambo began approximately
cuando empezó el mambo aproximadamente
smoke eh smoke smoke cloth of smoke eh I
humo eh humo humo tela de humo eh Te lo
told you Javi smoke smoke a lot of smoke Yes and
dije Javi humo humo mucho humo Sí y
well I have seen things and where I was
bueno he visto cosas e donde yo no salía
amazed basically I have gone I have been
de mi asombro básicamente yo he ido yo
seeing things that were not normal
he ido viendo cosas que no eran normales
okay And of course all this was getting bigger and
vale Y claro la todo esto se hacía cada
bigger I am going crazy it can't
vez más grande estoy volviendo loco no
be because here they played a lot with
puede ser porque aquí se jugó mucho con
the issue of the broken phone this is said
el tema del teléfono roto está dicho
this is said this this and it is I don't know what
esto está dicho esto esto y es no sé qué
And this I don't know how many and to me pam pam pamam pamam
Y este no sé cuántos y a mí pam pam
pam and then over there then
pamam pamam pam y luego por ahí luego
over there and then over there I say man I mean
por allá y luego por ahí digo tío o sea
what is happening here is not normal I mean I do
lo que está ocurriendo aquí no es normal
n't believe it is normal no It is
o sea No me creo que sea normal no Es
logical there is something that doesn't fit okay
lógico hay algo que no encaja vale
then the ball went It was getting
entonces la bola se fue Se fue haciendo
bigger and bigger and that is where I say
cada vez más grande y ahí es donde digo
if I do a recap of the year what I
si yo hago una recapitulación del año lo
see is in some live shows where I
que veo es en algunos directos donde yo
directly jump jump like a lame and boom
directamente salto salto de cojo y boum
jump and start saying outrageous things
salto y empiezo a decir barbaridades
when really it is not what I would have
cuando realmente no es lo que Tendría
that having done what I should have
que haber hecho lo que Tendría que haber
done is the same as in 2021 just
hecho es igual que en 2021 simplemente
sweat like always sweat no What is there
sudar como siempre sudar no En qué hay
another topic, I mean, you guys are
otro tema o sea vosotros sois
aware of the amount of
conscientes de la cantidad de acoso
absurd harassment that there has been throughout the
absurdo que ha habido durante todo el
year for nonsense I mean I want to emphasize
año por tonterías O sea quiero recalcar
one thing nothing serious has happened okay I
una cosa no ha pasado nada grave vale no
'm not apologizing what I'm
me estoy disculpando lo que estoy
saying is despite me having my
diciendo es a pesar de yo tener mis
reasons okay It's not the act And it
motivos vale No es la act ación Y
corresponds to my way of and my way of
corresponde a mi forma de y mi forma de
being is to ignore ignore and that's what
ser es ignorar ignorar y ya eso es lo
I should have done
que yo tendría que haber hecho durante
throughout the year simply then at the
todo el año simplemente luego a nivel de
community level at the community level It is true
comunidad a nivel de comunidad Es cierto
that I have had many slip-ups
que yo he tenido muchas patinadas en
live I recognize it I remember that I have
directo lo reconozco yo recuerdo que he
had live shows where it's that I don't even
tenido directos donde es que ni me
remember I apologize to my community
acuerdo Yo me disculpo con mi comunidad
this I mean no I don't want you to make
está O sea no no quiero que os monté
a movie here eh No no I
aquí una película eh No no yo me
apologize to my community and you know perfectly well
disculpo con mi comunidad y sabéis
how I am and this year
perfectamente cómo soy y este año se
there is a total disconnection saying
viste una desconexión total diciendo
this guy who the hell is What
este tío quién [__] es A qué le ha
happened to him Well the reason is very simple it has
pasado Pues el motivo es muy sencillo
simply been bam pamam everything and they have
simplemente ha sido bam pamam todo y
also heated me up  a lot The
también me han calentado mucho Los
helmets also to Caesar what is of the to
cascos también al César lo que es del a
me have heated up a lot The helmets cl
mí me han calentado mucho Los cascos cl
that has not helped in all this have
eso no ha ayudado en todo este me han
heated up a lot the thieves to Caesar what
calentado mucho los cacos al César lo
is of Caesar who does he refer to
que es del César a quién se refiere
when he says that the thieves have heated up
cuando dice que le han calentado los
who does he refer to that he has had
cacos a quén se refiere a que ha tenido
someone by his side putting [ __ ] on the
alguien al lado metiéndole [__] el
process and on the other hand then being
proceso y que por otra parte luego estar
in Boca of everyone that if the
en Boca de todo el mundo que si los
gossip that if this is I already say it and it will
salseos que si esto sea yo ya lo digo y
be Oh how annoying really man
va a ser Ay qué pesado de verdad tío
but cl a if you are fighting with
peroo cl a si te estás peleando con
someone Well of course you are going to be in
alguien Pues claro que vas a estar en
the gossip if you are saying that you
los salseos si estás diciendo que
want to denounce Auron's brother if you
quieres denunciar al hermano de auron si
are saying that you are going to destroy 10
estás diciendo que vas a destruir 10
careers permanently that I
carreras de forma permanente que yo
can make mistakes and I recognize them
puedo cometer errores y los reconozco
without any problem every time I
sin ningún problema cada vez que la
finish it I recognize issues gossip and so on and
acabo lo recono temas salseos y demás y
get into controversies and stand here to
entrar en polémicas y ponerme aquí a
defend myself such is finished I am not going
defenderme tal está terminado ya no voy
to feed people anymore simply here
a dar de comer a gente simplemente aquí
as you see scavenger that will never
como vres carroñero eso no volverá a
happen again never again we return to
pasar nunca más jamás volvemos a la
normal and normality is  I
normalidad y la normalidad es yo
streamer with my community and logically
streamer con mi comunidad y lógicamente
doing what I like creating content,
haciendo lo que me gusta crear contenido
I have not come here to stir things up, to
yo no he venido aquí a liar la parda a
be here with nonsense,
estar aquí con tonterías discusiones sin
meaningless discussions Because honestly, in
sentido Porque sinceramente yo con
hindsight, I see it and I say this, it's
retrospectiva lo veo y digo esto que es
in high school or what am I in
en instituto oa queé estoy en el
high school, damn, I'm 33 Alo, I really have
instituto [__] tengo 33 Alo de verdad he
returned to that time where there are fights,
vuelto a esa época donde son peleas de
pointless fights, I already said it, I
peleas sin sentido yo ya lo digo lo
anticipate it eh everything that is SEO is already
anticipo eh todo lo que sea el seo ya ha
over everything that is eh I who know how to
terminado todo lo que sea eh yo que sé
[ __ ] on someone's [ __ ] mother is
cagarme en la [__] madre de alguien tal
over I leave that behind for
se ha terminado eso lo dejo atrás para
me it's behind I don't want to know anything about
mí es atrás ya no quiero saber nada de
all this and I care very little about the
todo esto y me importa bien poco el
opportunism that I have seen a
oportunismo que he visto un oportunismo
cheap, vile opportunism and that of course has my
barato ruin y que por supuesto tiene mi
absolute, I mean my absolute and total
absoluto o sea mi absoluta y total
contempt, okay, of course, I think that
desprecio vale desde luego yo creo que
with that enough
ya con eso ya se entiende bastantes
things are understood, I come to the conclusion that
cosas llego a la conclusión de que
generally I am not understanding
generalmente que no estoy entendiendo
absolutely anything about the gymnastics that he is doing,
absolutamente nada de la gimnasia que
man, I mean What do you mean
está haciendo tío o sea A qué se refiere
by opportunism What do you mean by you
con el oportunismo A qué se refiere con
know, I mean What do you mean by the
sabes o sea A qué se refiere con el
opportunism who who taking advantage here
oportunismo quién quién aprovechado aquí
a clear opportunism an opportunism
un oportunismo claro un oportunismo
could be
podrían ser
m level of interest level of economic or
m nivel de interés nivel de económico o
level Like for example what happened with Auron no
nivel Como por ejemplo pasó con auron no
that when they were funding him
que cuando lo estaban funando el año
last year suddenly three or four came out from under the
pasado de repente salieron debajo de las
stones no eh To take
piedras tres o cuatro no eh Para
advantage no this is
aprovechar no este es el momento débil
Auro's weak moment here we give it to him no that we
de Auro aquí le damos no que le teníamos
wanted to before but the thing is that here he is not
ganas de antes pero es que aquí no está
speaking clearly and when he does not speak
hablando claro y yo cuando no habla
clearly people get really angry V the
claro la gente me da mucho coraje V los
clips because I do not understand a [ __ ]
clip porque no me entero de una [__]
thing he says a lot to not say anything in the
[__] dice mucho para no decir nada
end the people who are there are not
total la gente que está ahí pues no está
very well in the head sincerely they
muy bien de la cabeza sinceramente no
are not very well in the head and you do not have to
está muy bien de la olla y tampoco hay
understand anything simply I have
que entender nada simplemente yo he
read messages until this guy does not commit
leído mensajes de hasta que este tío no
suicide live it is going to be p p p
se suicida en directo va a ser p p p
this guy has to be how heavy Lili how
este tío tiene que qué heavy Lili qué
heavy This is going to be a special handsome handsome
heavy Esto va a ser un especial guapo
eh what Kevy has to be
guapo eh qué kevy tiene que estar
down such no how much and you will say I have
hundido tal no cuanto y tú dirás he
done something serious I have not killed someone
hecho algo grave no he matado a alguien
no eh I have killed a grandmother I have not
no eh Me he cargado una abuela no he
robbed someone no eh I have started
atracado a alguien no eh me he puesto
here doing disturbing things no  I've
aquí hacer cosas perturbadoras no he
done strange things with money No, I haven't
hecho cosas raras con dinero No no he
done absolutely anything and for you to say
hecho absolutamente nada y que digas
this guy, we have to go for it, no, it
este tío hay que ir a por no
's literally unjustifiable. I'm
literalmente es injustificable yo estoy
here to entertain and that's my
aquí para entretener Y esa es mi
intention, to entertain, everything else was unnecessary, it was
intención entretener todo lo demás
unnecessary, but a lot of taking,
sobraba sobraba pero mucho de [__]
answering and then starting there is a
contestar Y luego empezar hay una
toxic and absurd dynamic, unnecessary, it
dinámica tóxica y Absurda innecesario
contaminates everyone, it contaminates my
contamina a todo el mundo contamina a mi
community and in the end everything remains in what
comunidad y al final Todo queda en qué
nonsense. Well, no, no, my
en tontera pues no pues no lo mi
decision is what I've told you and that is that
decisión es lo que os he dicho y es que
from now on, despite the
a partir de ahora pese a las
defamation that is
difamaciones que se me hagan no
made against me, I will not answer despite the massive hatred that there is, I will not answer despite the gossip, I will not answer despite everything that has been done to me, I will not answer, I will not say absolutely nothing, I am not going to be part of this circle, an Orwellian circus in
de este círculo Circo orwelliano en el
which he has messed everything up, eh, he has messed
cual lo ha liado todo él eh lo ha liado
everything up and in the end he is blaming us
todo él y al final nos está culpando a
all for having spoken about the subject, for having
tod kisi por haber hablado del tema por
reacted, I can't take it anymore, eh, the
haber reaccionado yo no puedo más eh Los
vultures feed on it, that's
Buitres se alimentan de ello eso se ha
over, it's over, period, that's it,
terminado se ha terminado punto ya está
I assume my mistakes.  In front of my
yo asumo mis errores de Cara a mi
community I have even gone so far as to say
comunidad incluso he llegado a decir que
if you want to [ __ ] me or I don't know what I don't even
si queréis follarme o no sé qué Ya ni me
remember that live I remember
acuerdo de aquel directo Yo me acuerdo
that I was freaking out about these things
que estaba estaba flipando estas cosas
of course I apologize they have lied to me
por supuesto que yo me disculpo me han
and I believed it and that is
llegado a mentir y yo creerlo y ahí es
where breaking a rule that I have always
donde incumplir una norma que siempre he
said is what they tell you ironic eh
dicho es de lo que te digan irónico eh
the rule that I have always said since 2020
la regla que siempre he dicho desde 2020
what they tell you Do not believe anything And of
de lo que te digan No te creas nada Y de
what you see believe half ironically
lo que veas créete la mitad irónicamente
I fell into the error I fell into the [ __ ] error and
caí en el error caí en el [__] error y
that is already a matter of myself
eso ya es una cuestión de yo mismo
you understand myself then I have been
entiendes yo mismo luego me he ido
finding out as the
enterando a medida de que pasaban los
months went by I don't know if you are
meses Es que no sé si ustedes estáis
catching something that I am missing
pillando algo que a mí se me escapa
tell me man because he is talking about a
decirme tío porque está hablando un
broken phone he is talking about
teléfono roto está está hablando de que
someone he is talking about that
alguien le sea está hablando de que
someone has warmed his ear of course and
alguien le ha calentado la oreja claro y
here I don't know if you are falling into something that I am
aquí no sé si ustedes caé en algo que yo
not falling into because it is already 3 in
no estoy cayendo porque ya son las 3 de
the morning but of course I have the feeling
la mañana pero claro me da la sensación
that he is blaming someone a
de que está culpando a alguien a un
third party that could be a  buddy a
tercero que podría ser un compañero un
friend or someone who tells him things about
amigo o alguien que le dice cositas de
others or gives him [ __ ] about others
los demás o le mete [__] de los demás
and it's not true no no I don't know anymore
y que no es verdad no no ya no se ya no
he's not referring to the
está haciendo referencia a los canales
gossip channels his girlfriend but of course
de salseo la novia pero claro es que a
who does he have next to him rebot Here the only one
quién tiene al lado rebot Aquí el único
that turns us on is Javi Look man The
que nos calienta es Javi Mira tío La
truth is yes yes yes I turn you on a lot and
verdad sí sí sí os caliento muchísimo y
everything you want but I'm not here
todo lo que queráis pero yo aquí no me
Hey hey hey good question hey hey guys guys
Oye oye oye buena pregunta oye oye
guys good
chavales chavales chavales buena
question where is serene and serene
pregunta dónde está serene y serene
where is where is serene and serene and
where is where is serene y sereno y
serene Where is serene Hey uncle Ricky
sereno Dónde está sereno Oye tío Ricky
since you're so pissed off nothing will happen
ya que estás tan picado que no pasa nada
eh I could excuse you because you fell for
eh que podría disculparte porque caíste
the [ __ ] [ __ ] of your friend the inmate who
en la [__] [__] de tu amigo el recluso
invented the hitmen you did some
que se inventó los sicario hicisteis un
kind of pathetic acting eh I liked
acting un poco patético eh Me gustó más
your acting better when you cheated the other
tu acting cuando hiciste trampa el otro
day at the skip damn man that
día en los skip [__] tío es que eso no
couldn't be forgotten eh I mean the
podría quedar en el olvido eh o sea el
acting they did with the Serene thing
acting que hicieron con lo de serene
because the inmate from raed
porque se lo inventó el recluso de raed
just got out made it up  from prison the acting
recién salido de la prisión el acting
with the Serene thing dude, I mean RAE comes to him
con lo de serene tío o sea le viene RAE
dude RAED comes to him a guy who
tío le viene raed un tipo al que
was called a scammer before he
estuvieron llamando estafador antes de
fought with Dallas and he comes to them and he
que se peleara con Dallas y les viene r
says Well look at some hitmen and
les dice Pues mira unos sicari y el
Javit has hookups on Instagram to take it up
javit tiene ligues en instagram a tomar
the ass you know how to suck it and they pay attention to him
por el culo sabes a chuparla y le dan
dude and they pay attention to him and they're there so
bola tío y le dan bola y están ahí tan
so calm no but the delo the delos
tan campante no pero el delo el delos
like he's gotten out of the way no the
como que se ha quitado en medio no el
delo no longer he doesn't get involved in the gossip
delo ya no ya no entra no en los salseos
or he doesn't mess with anyone so there he
ni ni se mete con nadie entonces ahí
is Cool he even left me stranded
está Guay me ha dejado incluso tirado
a few things that I had to
unas cuantas de cosas que tenía que
send him so clear I tell you I'm
hacerle envío así de claro os lo digo me
happy for him but Ricky who doesn't
alegro por él pero el Ricky que no se
shut up dude and Ricky is like [ __ ] [ __ ]
calla tío y el Ricky es como cabrón
[ __ ] cut it out we're still
cabrón cabrón córtate que todavía
waiting for your
estamos esperando tu orden de
restraining order [ __ ] a lot of
alejamiento cabrón muchas cosas
unpleasant things that I didn't like at
desagradables que a mí no me gustaban
all and of course Ah she's the bomb the bomb the bomb the bomb the bomb
nada y claro Ah ella la bomba la bomba
I say
la bomba la bomba la bomba la bomba digo
Uy she can't but now that the bomb
Uy no puede pero ahora que la bomba se
has deflated a lot because I understood
ha desinflado mucho porque he entendido
many things I have also understood many
muchas cosas también he entendido muchas
things and I have realized and I am not the
cosas y me he dado cuenta y no soy el
only one but several people and
único sino varias personas y
indeed indeed here there have
efectivamente efectivamente aquí ha
been a lot of broken phones the classic
habido mucho teléfono roto el clásico
broken phone said that and the other I don't know
teléfono roto dicho eso y el otro no sé
what but no but I did not say that no no no
qué pero no pero yo no dije eso no no no
but yes this one has told me how about I do not know what
pero sí este me ha dicho qu tal no sé
guy this institute this what the [ __ ] are
qué tío este instituto esto qué [__] es
you is this [ __ ] so of course there already
tí es esta [__] entonces claro ahí ya
eh As I say There is a problem in private
eh Como digo Hay un problema en privado
as I have always done problem in
como siempre he hecho problema en
private the carrion wies well that is not
privado los wies carroñeros bueno que no
solved in private no problem
se solventa en privado ningún problema
is sweated and something else happens so I am
se suda y se pasa otra cosa así yo me
going to limit myself to what I have
voy a limitar a lo que siempre he hecho
always done I keep quiet I speak in private and if I have to take measures They will be the measures that I consider appropriate outside of Twitch I had eh a way of seeing things in which I fervently believed in
las cuales yo creía fervientemente en
work camaraderie but well this
compañerismo de trabajo pero bueno este
year I have seen things that have shown me
año he visto cosas que me han mostrado
that I have made mistakes I make it very clear that it will never
que he errado dejo bien claro que jamás
happen again I make it very
volverá a ocurrir nunca lo dejo bien
clear no matter how much they look for me it will not
claro por mucho que me busquen no va a
happen in private or through the means that I
pasará en privado o por las vías que yo
consider appropriate
considero oportunas humo
humid smoke is very very very strong eh
humífero es muy muy muy fuerte eh Ya
We'll talk calmly later
hablaremos tranquilamente
[Music]
[Música]